ethexindia.com 2017-06-06

# Terms & Conditions -ETHEXIndia

## Privacy **Policy**

The ETHEXIndia.com website and ETHEXIndia are part of S Capital Solutions India Pvt. LTD. At ETHEXIndia we consider that the privacy and security of personal and financial information/details of our customers as our highest concern. We have designed and implemented policies and procedures to protect our costumer information. The following document is our privacy policy. By using ETHEXIndia.com you are accepting our privacy policy.

### 1\. The Information We Gather

\- We may collect details from our customers such as name, date of birth, address, phone number and other identity information issued by Government of India for identification purposes. These(this?) information is required to provide hassle free and accurate services to our customers. The information collected is used to provide specific product offerings, maintain and administer crypto currency trading services and provide information about our future offerings to our customers.

\- Pertaining ETHEXIndia.com, we may collect specific information such as e-mail addresses, page request information and transaction activity on the website. The information such as the IP addresses, browser information, operating system and other MIME information will also be collected. This information may be used to identify the ISPs and geographical information which in turn are used to better serve our customers.

### 2\. How we use your information

Your personal information may be used to for the following:

  1. To verify the identity and the authenticity of the customer information (KYC compliance) 
  2. To facilitate transactions 
  3. To provide customized services 
  4. To authenticate and provide customer support 
  5. To develop new products and refine existing services 
  6. To contact you whenever needed 
  7. To perform quick checks while transactions are being performed 
  8. To verify citizenship 
  9. To comply with the regulatory bodies and the government organizations for verification and investigation 
  10. To comply with fraud detection 
  11. To prevent phishing and other social engineering activities 
  12. To train our staff to provide better service 
  13. To inform you with special offers and other promotional activities 

### 3\. Phishing

\- ETHEXIndia exercises care while sending mails to you. In case of any mail other than business mails referring to ETHEXIndia or ETHEXIndia.com seems to be suspicious the you should immediately contact ETHEXIndia Support and verify the credibility of the mail. 

### 4\. Links to Other Websites:

\- ETHEXIndia.com may contain links to third party websites and other resources which may have their own privacy policy. ETHEXIndia holds no responsibility for the data entered into third party links and urges you to go through the respective privacy policies. 

### 5\. Opting out of marketing, promotions or related activities

\- ETHEXIndia may contact you regarding promotions, service/product launches, feedback and surveys. If the you wish to opt out of the above said activities, you may write to support@ethexindia.com or call Customer Support using your registered phone number.

### 6\. Security

\- ETHEXInida gives high priority to customer information and all measures are taken care to safeguard the information by taking appropriate measures to avoid unauthorized access, tampering or destruction. The measures may include encryption of highest standard, physical access restriction among others. In spite of taking stringent measures, transactions over internet are vulnerable for attacks. This may be noted and you are urged to take necessary precautions at your end while performing transactions. 

### 7\. Cookies 

\- ETHEXIndia.com uses cookies in the web browsers to store relevant information. The cookies are used to better understand how our customers interact with our websites and services and to improve our websites and services overall. The functionality of our website is highly dependent on the cookies that we use. The cookie remains on the computer after browser is closed and may be used by the browser on subsequent visits to our websites.

**Note:** If you do not wish to have cookies placed on your computer, please set your browser to refuse cookies before visiting our websites and using our services. This may however hamper the functionality of ETHEXIndia.com on your computer.

### 8\. Changes

ETHEXIndia may make changes to this privacy policy from time to time to ensure compliance and other factors. Please check this page from time to time for any changes. 

* * *
